Guide to the Stanford University, Faculty Senate, Records SC0193
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Academic Council records, 1891-1989; Accession ARCH_1989_214
  - Tapes of the Senate of the Academic Council, Senate XIX-XX, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
    - Senate XIX (2 of 2), 1987 Feb 19; 16_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 9)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 2), 1987 Mar 5; 16_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 10)
    - Senate XIX (2 of 2), 1987 Mar 5; 16_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 11)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 3), 1987 Apr 2; 16_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 12)
    - Senate XIX (2 of 3), 1987 Apr 2; 16_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 13)
    - Senate XIX (3 of 3), 1987 Apr 2; 16_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 14)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 2), 1987 May 7; 16_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 15)
    - Senate XIX (2 of 2), 1987 May 7; 16_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 16)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 2), 1987 May 21; 16_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 17)
    - Senate XIX (2 of 2), 1987 May 21; 16_18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 18)
    - Senate XIX (1 of 2), 1987 Jun 11; 16_19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 19)
    - Senate XIX (2 of 2), 1987 Jun 11; 16_20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 20)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1987 Oct 1; 16_21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 21)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1987 Oct 1; 16_22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 22)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1987 Oct 15; 16_23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 23)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1987 Oct 15; 16_24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 24)
    - Senate XX (1 of 1), 1987 Oct 29; 16_25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 25)
    - Senate XX (1 of 1), 1987 Nov 12; 16_26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 26)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1987 Dec 3; 16_27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 27)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1987 Dec 3; 16_28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 28)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1988 Jan 7; 16_29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 29)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1988 Jan 7; 16_30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 30)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1988 Jan 21; 16_31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 31)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1988 Jan 21; 16_32; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 32)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1988 Feb 4; 16_33; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 33)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1988 Feb 4; 16_34; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 34)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1988 Feb 18; 16_35; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 35)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1988 Feb 18; 16_36; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 36)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1988 Mar 3; 16_37; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 37)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1988 Mar 3; 16_38; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 16, Item 38)
  - Tapes of the Senate of the Academic Council, 1971-1989 (Box 17)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1988 Mar 31; 17_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 1)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1988 Mar 31; 17_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 2)
    - Senate XX (1 of 1), 1988 Apr 14; 17_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 3)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1988 Apr 28; 17_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 4)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1988 Apr 28; 17_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 5)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1988 May 5; 17_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 6)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1988 May 5; 17_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 7)
    - Senate XX (1 of 1), 1988 May 12; 17_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 8)
    - Senate XX (1 of 2), 1988 May 26; 17_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 9)
    - Senate XX (2 of 2), 1988 May 26; 17_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 10)
    - Senate XX (1 of 1), 1988 Jun 9; 17_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 11)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1971 Oct 1; 17_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 12)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1972 Mar 3; 17_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 13)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1972 Mar 31; 17_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 14)
    - Academic Council (1 of 2), 1972 Sept 29; 17_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 15)
    - Academic Council (2 of 2), 1972 Sept 29; 17_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 16)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1973 Jan 5; 17_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 17)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1973 Oct 3; 17_18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 18)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1976 Apr 2; 17_19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 19)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1978 Jan 6; 17_20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 20)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1978 Sept 29; 17_21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 21)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1979 Jan 5; 17_22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 22)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1979 Sept 28; 17_23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 23)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1980 Jan 18; 17_24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 24)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1980 Apr 4; 17_25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 25)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1980 Oct 3; 17_26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 26)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1981 Jan 9; 17_27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 27)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1981 Apr 3; 17_28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 28)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1981 Oct 2; 17_29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 29)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1982 Jan 8; 17_30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 30)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1982 Apr 9; 17_31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 31)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1982 Oct 8; 17_32; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 32)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1983 Feb 3; 17_33; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 33)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1983 Apr 1; 17_34; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 34)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1983 Oct 12; 17_35; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 35)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1985 May 16; 17_36; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 36)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1986 May 1; 17_37; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 37)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1986 Nov 20; 17_38; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 38)
    - Academic Council (1 of 1), 1989 Apr 18; 17_39; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17, Item 39)
- Academic Council records, Accession ARCH_1989_217
  - General Correspondence, "A" (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, "Ba" (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, "Bm-Br" (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, "Bs-Bz" (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, "Ca-Cg" (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, "Ch-Co" (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, "Coa-Cg" (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, "Cp-Cz" (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Academic Calendar (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - A-21 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Academic Council Runs, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Academic Executive Officers (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adjunct Professoriate (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Board, 1978- (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Organization (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Admissions, 1950-June 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Affirmative Action Annual Reports (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Association (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - American Association of University Professors (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Associates of Stanford University Libraries (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ASSU, 1975- (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ASSU, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ASSU, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Awards (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Professor William Bonner-Chemistry Department (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Symposium on British Isles, 29502 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Budget-Academic Secretary's Office (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Building 170-Renovation (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cambodia (responses from Congress), 1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Campaign for Stanford (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Charonnat, Jeffery A. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Churchill Scholarship (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - C. I. A. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Combined Stanford Appeals Campaign (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Commencement (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Computer System, 1981- (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Controller, 1963- (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Courses and Degrees (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Stanford Curriculum Study, 30608 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - General Correspondence "D" (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Daily (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Dean of Students (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - General Correspondence "E" (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Earthquakes (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Report on Stanford Emeriti, 28689 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Endowed Professorships (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Endowed Scholarships and Fellowships (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - General Correspondence "F" (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Faculty (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Club, 23986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Early Faculty Retirement Program (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Financial Forecasts, 1981- (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Studies Program (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Forum on International Policy (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Seminar Program (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence "G" (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General Secretary (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Convocation, 29855 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Graphics and Printing (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Inaugural Committee (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Inauguration of President Kennedy, 29506 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Information Bulletin (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Inner Quad Renovation Project (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Inquiries to Academic Secretary (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "I" Center (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence "J" (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Judicial, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Judicial, 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence "K" (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence "La-Lk" (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence "Ll-Lz" (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Law School (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Lecturers (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Lewis, J.W. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Liquor (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Pres. R.W. Lyman (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence "Ma-Md" (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - General Correspondence "Me-Mh" (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence "Mi-Mz" (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Management Development Program (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Maps (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Media and the Senate (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Medical School (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Medical School Teaching (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Memos (Stanford) (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - General Correspondence "N" (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - News Service (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - General Correspondence "O" (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Memorial Church (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - MT/ST (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - William F. Miller (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Ombudsman (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - General Correspondence "Pa-Pn" (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - General Correspondence "Po-Pz" (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Panel on the M.A. Degree in Teaching (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Patents (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Personnel (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Pitzer, K.S. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Search Committee (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - President's Dinner, 26001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - President's Office, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Principles Procedures...Ballots (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Press Coverage-Senate Meetings (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Professional Journalism Fellows (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Provostial Search Committee (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Provost's Office, 1973- (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Provost's Office, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Public Affairs Fellows (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Equipment Purchases (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Q miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - General correspondence R (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Recommendations (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Registrar (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Registrar - Editorial secretary (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Registrar - Statistics (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Reapportionment (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Regulations governing student conduct (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Research (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Research associates (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Resident fellows (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Retirement - Faculty (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Retirement - staff employees, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rosters, 1985-86 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Rosters, 1984-85 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Rosters, 1983-84 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Committee Rosters, 1983-84 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Unions (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - University Relations (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - General Correspondence "University of Aa-Univ. of Minnesota" (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - General Correspondence "Univ. of Na-Univ. of Pz" (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - General Correspondence "Univ. of Qa-Univ. of Uz" (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - General Correspondence "V" (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Values, Technology, and Society (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Visitors-Academic Secretary's Office (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - General Correspondence "Wa-Wh" (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - General Correspondence "Wi-Wz" (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - General Corerspondence "Y" (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Washington Delegation (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Rosters, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Rosters, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Rosters, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Rosters, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Rosters, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Rosters, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Rosters, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Rosters, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Rosters, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Rosters, 1973- (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rosters, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ROTC (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence "Sa-Sd" (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence "Se-Sh" (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence "Si-So" (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence "Sp-Std" (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence "Ste-Sz" (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Search for Provost, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Search Committees, 1978- (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Selectvie Service (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Senate, General File (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Senior Survey, 1981- (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - SPOSS (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - SPO (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Historical Society (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Stanford in Washington, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Publications (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - SSAM-COIN II (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Staff Development Courses (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1953- (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Study of Education at Stanford (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence "Ta-Th" (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence "Ti-Tz" (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Tenure Statement (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Trees (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Board of Trustees (Files #1-#3) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Trustees, 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Trustees (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Tuition (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Union Material (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Memorial Resolutions
    - Abbot, Donald P. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Arbuckle, Ernest C. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Bailey, Thomas A. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Bailey, Margery (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Barnett, Charles W. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Britt, Richard H. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Leland (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Berman, Lawrence (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Buck, Philip W. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Carrington, Charles R. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Chan, S. Wing (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Chilton, Ernest Gunther (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Cox, Allan V. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Crimson, Jefferson M. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Dowley, Edith M. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Feigen, George A. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Flory, Paul J. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Fuchs, Henry O. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Geiman, Quentin (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Gonda, Thomas A. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Grant, Ronald (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Gray, Donald James (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Green, Boynton M. (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Greulich, William Walter (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Guthrie, Luell W. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Hadari, Saguiv A. (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Hanna, Paul R. (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Hawley, Newton S. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Working, Holbrook (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Holm, Richard W. (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Howard, Arthur D. (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Howard, Donald R. (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Hulbut, John B. (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Jameson, Robert M. (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Keen, A. Myra (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - La Piere, Richard T. (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Leighton, Philip A. (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Liu, James Jo-Yu (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Mc Gregor, James (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Mc Lennan, Charles E. (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Mc Lennan, Margaret T. (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Mc Nemar, Quinn (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Mason, David M. (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Meyers, Charles J. (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Miller, Rupert G. (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Myers, George Sprague (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Neumark, S. Daniel (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Pearson, Gerald L. (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Pearson, Lionel I.C. (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Pettit, Joseph M. (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Polya, George (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Oliphant, Joseph F. (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Pound, Guy M. (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Rathbun, Harry J. (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Raubitschek, Isabelle K. (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Rhinelander, Philip (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Scott, Gordon K. (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Schramm, Wilbur (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Seltzer, Leon E. (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Sterling, J.E. Wallace (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Strathairn, Pamela L. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Stuart, Graham H. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Szego, Gabor (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Van Neil, Cornelis (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Van Patten, Nathan (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Wiggins, Ira L. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Academic Council records, Accession ARCH_1989_224
  - Trustee Committees (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Honor Code Commission (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Committees-Miscellaneous, 1978-79 and 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Committees-Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Academic Calendar (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Academic Staff Affairs (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Panel on Internal Athletic, Physical Education and Recreational Programs (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Committee on University Budget Priorities (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Committee on University Budget Adjustment Program (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Cable Television (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dinkelspiel, 1972- (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dinkelspiel, 1956-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Education and Employment of Women in the University, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Education and Employment of Women in the University, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Education and Employment of Women in the University, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Education and Employment of Women in the University, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Engineering General Program (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Faculty Handbook, 1970-1979 and 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ad Hoc Task Force on Disclosure of Faculty Salaries (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Panel of Reviewing Officers for Level III of Grievance Procedure for Grad Students, etc. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - History of Science Committee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Housing Advisory Committee (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Low Cost Housing, 1968-69 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Committee on International Studies (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Long Range Planning (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Memberships and Privileges (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Minority Affairs (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Operations Review Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Review Academic Programs in P.E. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Committee on Presidential Selection (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Administrative Panel on Retirement (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Task Force on Retirement Policies (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Scope, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Search Committees (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Task Force on Sponsored Research Volume (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Committee to Study SRI, 1968-70 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Golf Course Advisory Committee, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - KZSU Board (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Study of Education at Stanford (SES), 1967-71 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Study of Graduate Education at Stanford University, 1970-73 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Study the Length of Terms of Academic Instruction (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Education and Humanities, Joint Doctoral Program (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Committee on Staff and Faculty Services (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Relations with Student Government, 1968-69 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Student Participation in Political Processes (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board of Tellers, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Committee of Tellers, 1979-80; 1978-79; 1977-78 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Committee of Tellers (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tresidder Advisory Committee and Committee on Tresidder Union (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1955-56 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Unexcused Absences, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - COUP [Committee on University Policy], 1964-67 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Western Culture Program (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Advisory Panel on Tresidder Union Board (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Provost's Advisory Committee on Budget Planning, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Provost's Advisory Committee on Archeology (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Panel on Lab Animal Care, 1978- (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Academic Council records, 1891-1910; Accession ARCH_1989_231
  - Academic Council minutes, June 4, 1904 - June 10, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, Academic Council, minutes, June 10, 1904 - June 13, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Record of the Proceedings in Faculty Meetings, October 1891 - February 1904 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Faculty Senate meetings [audio recordings], 1983-1993; Accession ARCH_1993_107
  - Senate XXI, 1988-1989
    Scope and Contents
    Records dated 9/29/88, 10/13/88, 10/27/88, 11/10/88, 12/01/88, 1/12/89, 1/26/89, 2/09/89, 2/23/89, 3/09/89.
    - Senate XXI (1 of 1), 1988 Sept 9; 1_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 1)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1988 Oct 13; 1_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 2)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1988 Oct 13; 1_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 3)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1988 Oct 27; 1_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 4)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1988 Oct 27; 1_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 5)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1988 Nov 10; 1_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 6)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1988 Nov 10; 1_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 7)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1988 Dec 1; 1_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 8)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1988 Dec 1; 1_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 9)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 1), 1989 Jan 12; 1_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 10)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1989 Jan 26; 1_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 11)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1989 Jan 26; 1_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 12)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1989 Feb 9; 1_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 13)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1989 Feb 9; 1_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 14)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1989 Feb 23; 1_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 15)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1989 Feb 23; 1_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 16)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1989 Mar 9; 1_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 17)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1989 Mar 9; 1_18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1, Item 18)
  - Senate XXI, 1989
    Records dated: 4/6/89, 4/20/89, 5/4/89, 5/18/89, 6/1/89, 6/15/89; Tapes for Senate XXII: 9/28/89, 10/12/89, 11/9/89, 11/30/89
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1989 Apr 6; 2_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 1)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1989 Apr 6; 2_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 2)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2), 1989 Apr 20; 2_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 3)
    - Senate XXI, 1989 Apr 20; 2_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 4)
    - Senate XXI (1 of 2); Academic Senate, 1989 May 4; 1989 May 21; 2_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 5)
    - Senate XXI (2 of 2), 1989 May 4; 2_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2, Item 6)